the security in the police station is tight they'll figure you out in no time flat
so when a manhunt gets started no matter what powers you have you'll be stuck
meaning your only way of escape is taking the back streets behind the station
the problem with that is those streets have surveillance cameras all over if i send a
car for you it'll be spotted and from there they could easily follow our trail
so to avoid the cameras we'll have to resort to certain measures
and that will take muscle
i'm surprised the wang juan case is closed huh where are you taking those to
oh well um we're not done they just need some fresh air and something to eat
oh well you should have eaten by now and wait what about the captain
don't worry i'll pick up something for him later
oh go ahead then night
not every day we get to see wang smile it's a nice surprise she's always so stern
when you leave through the back door head straight to the next neighborhood
there are a lot of surveillance cameras along the roads but just on the other side of that area
you'll come across an old town that's currently under renovation
the residents have been relocated and the buildings are half destroyed
so the security system is obsolete
i'll arrange to have a few vehicles nearby to keep the police preoccupied
it'll be like you're walking into a thick fog
no one will be able to find you
they'll be able to find you
no one will be able to find the streets
no one will be able toai
no one will be able to find you